Guide to the Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1948-2019; 5680-004; 4.27 cubic feet (3 boxes and 1 tube) and 1 OS folder
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Compliance with Local Union Fiduciary and Recordkeeping Requirements, 2014 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Sample Credit Card Agreement & Expense Form, Undated (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 1384 Green Supply Order Sheet, 2014 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Supply Order Form, Undated (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Committee on Political Education Remittance Report, Undated (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Pink Sheet Forms, Undated (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union White Sheet Forms, Undated (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Green Sheet Forms, Undated (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Blue Sheet Forms, Undated (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Dues Deduction Authorization Cards, Undated (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union COPE Authorization Deduction Cards, Undated (Box-folder 1/12)
  - An Important Message from Your UNION stickers, Undated (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Withdrawl Cards, Undated (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Application for Membership, Undated (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Various ATU Pins & Buttons, 2012, 2016 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union 2014 Local Directory (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Directory 2015 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit Terms and Conditions of Employment for Rail Employees, 2013 (Box-folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit Transit Terms and Conditions of Employment, 2013 (Box-folder 1)
  - The Motorman, Conductor and Motor Coach Operator 1948 & 1952 (Box-folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 News Review, 2017 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union In Transit May/ June 2016 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union International Convention Niagara Falls Full Time Officer Picture, 2016 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 1)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2015 (Box-folder 1)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2016 (Box-folder 1)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2015-2016 (Box-folder 1)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2016-2017 (Box-folder 1)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2017 (Box-folder 1)
  - Transit Operator Samuel Ross Williams Obituary and Button, 1953-2016 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Michael Shea for Vice President Campaign card and Button, 2015 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Picture of Paul Bachtel in Scuba Suit, Undated (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Former Officers Group Photos, Undated (Box-folder 1/25)
  - The 587 Handbook - A guide to our Union, 2005 (Box-folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 News Review, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 2/1-2/8)
  - Metro Route Book March 11 - Sept 22, 2017 (Box-folder 2)
  - Metro Route Book Sept 23, 2017 - March 9, 2018, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 2)
  - Metro Route Book March 10, 2019 - Sept 21, 2019 (Box-folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 - 2018 Officer Elections (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union International - 2016 Local Directory (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2004, 2001 (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2007, 2004 (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2010, 2007 (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2010 (Rail Addendum), 2007 (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2013, 2010 (Box-folder 2)
  - Agreement Between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 and King County Metro Transit, Expiration Date October 31, 2016, 2013 (Box-folder 2)
  - Labor Agreement by and Between Jefferson Transit Authority and Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 - January 1, 2014 through December 31, 2017 (Box-folder 2)
  - Labor Agreement by and Between Clallam Transit System Fixed Route/Maint and Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 - January 1, 2015 through December 31, 2017 (Box-folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union International - Constitution and General Bylaws as amended 2013 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - The Book - 2016 (Box-folder 2)
  - The Book - 2017 (Box-folder 2)
  - Labor Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 & Solid Ground, 2012-2015 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Agreement by and between Kitsap Transit and Evergreen State Division No. 1384 of the ATU-CIO, 2015-2018 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Terminations & NDMT Grievances, Unknown (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Cards & Postcards, 2012-2017 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Various Photos + Washington Decal, 2012-2018 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Benjamin Haney for President, 2015 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Seattle Times Article, December 1, 2016, Honoring a bus driver killed in the line of duty (Box-folder 2/17)
  - ATU Local 587 News Review, 2015 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Campaign Information and Buttons, Undated (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Union Correspondence from Joe Mangiameli, 2013 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Advanced Shop Steward Training Holding Greivance Hearings, 1986 (Box-folder 3)
  - Centennial Celebration from ATU Local 587, 2012 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees of America, Undated (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Various Photos, Undated (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Memorandum of Agreement between Amalagamated Transit Union, Local 587 and the Clallam Transit System, 2015 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - ATU Local Union Directory, Undated (Box-folder 3)
  - Amalgamted Transit Union 2011 Local Union Directory (Box-folder 3)
  - Amalgamted Transit Union Local Directory, 2012 (Box-folder 3)
  - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO - Directory of Labor Organizations in Washington State, 2013 (Box-folder 3)
  - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO - Directory of Labor Organizations in Washington State, 2011 (Box-folder 3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union 2013 Local Directory (Box-folder 3)
  - A History of the Amalgamated Transit Union 1892-1992 (Box-folder 3)
  - In Loving Memory John A. Akerly, 2014 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Costco 1 Hour Photo Standing Tall with ATU Pride, 2011 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - The 587 Handbook - A guide to our Union, 2005 (Box-folder 3)
  - ATU Local 587 - 2012 Officer Elections (Box-folder 3)
  - ATU Local 587 - 2009 Officer Elections (Box-folder 3)
  - ATU Local 587 - 2015 Officer Elections (Box-folder 3)
  - Labor Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Directory of Elected Officials, 2012 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Metro Transit Contract Survey and Ballot Counts, 2013 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - A Message from your Bargaining Team to the Membership Regarding Negotiations, 2014 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Report, 2015 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Contract Changes, 1977-1995 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Rail Supplemental Agreement, 2006 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union JTA Members' Dues, 2015 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Notices of Election for First Transit, Inc., 2014 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Contract Survey, 2016 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Labor Agreement by and betwen Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 & Solid Ground, Undated (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Labor Agreement by and between Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 & Seattle Personal Transit, 2012 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 SPT Contract Survey, 2012 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Various Amalgamated Transit Union Pins & Buttons, Unknown (Box-folder 3/22)
  - The Book - Transit Operator's Rules and Procedures Revised September 2014 (Box-folder 3)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2015 (Box-folder 3)
  - King County Metro Route Book, 2015 (Box-folder 3)
  - MOA's Effective Contract, 2010-2013 (Box-folder 3/23-3/25)
  - By-Laws Rules & Regulations, 1900-1994 (Box-folder 3/26-3/28)
  - One Amalgamated Transit Union United Poster, Undated (Box-folder OS)
  - Local Elected Officials and Coalition Partners, Undated (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union For Hillary Poster 2016 (Box-folder OS)
  - King County Metro 2015 Year Poster (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 2012-2015 Officer Group Picture (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Executive Board Photo, 2009 (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Executive Board Photo, 2012 (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 Executive Board Photo, 2015 (Box-folder OS)
  - Metro Operators of the Year, 2014 (Box-folder OS)
  - Sign Amalgamated Transit Union Irene Hull Poster, Undated (Box-folder OS)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587 King County Negotiations Notes, 2016-2017 (Box-folder Tube)